[EPIC]⚡ It's Twilight time
[EPIC]⚡ Out of the east...
[EPIC]⚡ Wanda and Vision, aren't we a fine pair?
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Yes.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 This is our home now.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 I want us to fit in.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Oh, this is gonna be a gas!
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Where did you two move from?
[DIALOGUE]🗣 How long have you been married,
[DIALOGUE]🗣 and why don't you have children yet?
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Our story.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 I think what my wife means to say is that we moved
[DIALOGUE]🗣 from...
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Moved from where?
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Married when?
[EPIC]⚡ Damn it, why?
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Oh, Arthur, stop it.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Stop it!
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Stop it! Stop it!
[EPIC]⚡ This is really happening.
[EPIC]⚡ Am I dead?
[EPIC]⚡ No.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Why would you think that?
Because you are.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Usual couple, you know?
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Oh, I don't think that was ever in question.